# KEEGAN SECK

## **OBJECTIVE**

As a graduate of the UCSC Film and Digital Media degree program, I am well equipped for professional media production in any capacity. My education provides me with strong technical skills in film editing, where my experience with programs such as Adobe Premiere creates high-quality, professional content. Additionally, I worked in large teams to collaborate on complex film and live television projects, leading teams with my strong direction and organization skills. My long-term goal is to join a film or television production company to bring my powerful skill set and unique vision into the digial media age.

#### EDUCATION

Period	September 2012 — March 2017	
Degree	Bachelor of Arts in Film and Digital Media, Production Concentration	
University	University of California Santa Cruz	Santa Cruz, California

### Experience

_		
Perio	o April 2019 — August 2019	
Rol	E Production Intern	
Сомран	y Contra Costa Television	Martinez, California
Perio	September 2019 — Current	
Rol	E Production Assistant, Editor, Cameraman	
Сомран	y Contractor for Contra Costa Television	Martinez, California

## Skills

Writing	Developed strong writing abilities for film and digital media. Proficient technical and creative skills, with effective use of feedback.
Video	Experience with Adobe Premiere for televised and personal projects. Worked
Editing	alongside other students, clients, co-workers and alone to create professional
	content.
Filmmaking	Worked with audio and visual equipment for film production, including pro-
	ficient camera work.
Computer	Working skills with enterprise computer processes and services. Experience
Skills	with programming languages with a large capacity for learning.
Organization	Years of experience working with complicated organizations and groups. Un-
	derstands effective group interaction and team management.